{
  "chapter": 11,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "For which among the resource(s) the load balancing in computing is done?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Processor", "Storage", "Memory", "All of these"],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "In distributed computing environment, the load balancing is done for",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Servers",
        "Network Switches",
        "Storage",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Load balancing helps to implement the",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "System over-utilization",
        "System under-utilization",
        "System scaling",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Static load balancing approach does not consider the existing states of systems. This statement is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Requests from clients in cloud environment first appear in",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Front-end node",
        "Back-end node",
        "Depends on type of request",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In load balancing, resource provisioning happens before VM provisioning. This statement is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In which kind of load balancing, the feedback about existing load status are required?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Static", "Automatic", "Dynamic", "All of these"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following problem(s) may be caused by centralized load balancing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To many messages",
        "Bottleneck",
        "No feedback",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Class-aware load balancing algorithms are more critical in nature. This statement is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Session persistency in load balancing is maintained through",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In-memory session database",
        "Cookies",
        "None of these",
        "Both a and b"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Improving application serverâ€™s performance by offloading computeintensive tasks is known as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Task offloading",
        "Performance tuning",
        "Application acceleration",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]
}
